<resources>
    <!-- All recipes are referenced from food.com-->
    <string name="app_name">Final Project</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="recipe_name_one">Crock-Pot Chicken With Black Beans &amp; Cream Cheese</string>
    <string name="ingredient_one">
        4 -5 boneless chicken breasts, frozen\n
        1 (15 ounce) can corn                \n
        1 (15 ounce) jar salsa, any kind     \n
        1 (15 1/2 ounce) can black beans     \n
        1 (8 ounce) package cream cheese     \n
    </string>
    <string name="direction_one">
        Take 4-5 frozen, yes, frozen, boneless chicken breasts put into crock pot.\n
        Add 1 can of black beans, drained, 1 jar of salsa, 1 can of corn drained.\n
        Keep in crock pot on high for about 4-5 hours or until chicken is cooked.\n
        Add 1 package of cream cheese (just throw it on top!) and let sit for about 1/2 hour.\n
        All done and enjoy!\n
        Take 4-5 frozen, yes, frozen, boneless chicken breasts put into crock pot.\n
        Add 1 can of black beans, drained, 1 jar of salsa, 1 can of corn drained.\n
        Keep in crock pot on high for about 4-5 hours or until chicken is cooked.\n
        Add 1 package of cream cheese (just throw it on top!) and let sit for about 1/2 hour.\n
        All done and enjoy!\n
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_custom_dialog">CustomDialog</string>
    <string name="recipe_name_two">Beef and Zucchini Pasta Skillet Meal</string>
    <string name="ingredient_two">
        1 lb sirloin steak (cut into 1-inch cubes)
        \n1 teaspoon steak seasoning (spicy flavor)
        \n2 tablespoons canola oil (divided)
        \n1 small vidalia onion (sliced thin)
        \n2 garlic cloves (minced)
        \n2 (15 1/2 ounce) cans beef broth (low fat and low sodium)
        \n1 (15 ounce) can tomato sauce
        \n/2 lb ditalini (or other long tubular pasta)
        \n2 zucchini (diced into 1/4 inch cubes)
        \n2 Italian tomatoes (diced)
        \nbasil (to taste)
    </string>
    <string name="direction_two">
        Cut steak into 1-inch cubes.
        \nSeason with the spicy steak seasoning.
        \nIn large non-stick skillet, heat 1 tablespoon of oil over medium-high heat.
        \nAdd steak and cook until browned all over (approximately 3-5 minutes).
        \nRemove steak to a plate and cover to keep warm.
        \nAdd and heat the remaining 1 tablespoon of oil in skillet.
        \nAdd thinly sliced onion and minced cloves of garlic - saute 5 minutes.
        \nAdd beef broth and tomato sauce and bring to a boil.
        \nAdd pasta and cover skillet.
        \nSimmer for 8 minutes - stirring often.
        \nAdd thickly diced (1/4 inch) zucchini and cook covered until zucchini is crisp-tender (approximately 6-8 minutes).
        \nReturn steak to skillet and add diced tomatoes.
        \nHeat everything through for 1 minute.
        \nTop with basil (to your taste) before serving.
    </string>
    <string name="recipe_name_three">Crock Pot Hawaiian Chicken One-Dish Meal</string>
    <string name="ingredient_three">
        1 1/4 lbs chicken tenderloins
		\n2 tablespoons soy sauce
		\n2 medium carrots, sliced
		\n1 (8 ounce) can sliced water chestnuts
		\n1 (8 ounce) can pineapple chunks
		\n1/2 cup sweet and sour sauce
		\n2 teaspoons cornstarch
		\n1/2 teaspoon ginger
		\n1 (9 ounce) package frozen oriental-style vegetables
    </string>
    <string name="direction_three">
	Combine chicken and soy sauce in slow cooker and mix to coat. Stir in carrots, water chestnuts, and juice only from pineapples.
	\nCook on Low setting for 3 to 4 hours. Refrigerate pineapples until later.
	\nTwenty minutes before serving, turn heat to High setting. Whisk together sweet and sour sauce, ginger, and cornstarch. Add to crock pot, along with pineapple and vegetables.
	\nWhen vegetables are tender, the dish is ready to serve or hold on low. I often serve with white rice.
	</string>
    <string name="recipe_name_four">Crispy Baked Chicken Leg Quarters</string>
    <string name="ingredient_four">
	\n4 skin-on chicken leg quarters, with bone
	\n1/2 cup soy sauce, divided
	\n1 teaspoon garlic powder, divided
	\n1 teaspoon seasoning salt, divided
	\n1 teaspoon dill weed, divided
	</string>
    <string name="direction_four">
	\nPreheat oven to 375.
	\nLine a large glass baking dish with foil.
	\nRemove excess fat from chicken quarters.
	\nSeparate the skin from the chicken, taking care that the skin stays attached at most points on the chicken. (You just want a flap. Do not remove the skin).
	\nBrush the chicken (under the skin) with soy sauce.
	\nSprinkle some garlic powder, seasoned salt and dill weed on the chicken under the skin (I estimated the 1 tsp measures. Use as much or as little as you\'re comfortable with) and rub into the chicken.
	\nArrange the leg quarters in the pan, skin side up, taking care not to crowd. They need space to cook properly.
	\nBrush both sides of the leg quarters with soy sauce.
	\nSprinkle the skin with garlic powder, seasoned salt and dill weed (to taste).
	\nPlace on middle rack in over and bake uncovered for an hour.
	\nAfter an hour, increase oven temp to 400 and bake 15 minutes.
	\nChicken is done when internal temp reaches 165 (insert meat thermometer at thickest part of thigh, taking care not to touch the bone).
	\nLet stand for 5 minutes before serving
	</string>
    <string name="recipe_name_five">Onion Pot Roast</string>
    <string name="ingredient_five">
	\n1 tablespoon vegetable oil
	\n3 lbs boneless beef rump roast or 3 lbs blade roast
	\n1 onion, chopped
	\n2 cups beef broth
	\n1⁄2 cup apple juice
	\n1⁄2 cup red wine
	\n1 (1 ounce) packet onion soup mix
	\n1⁄2 teaspoon dried thyme
	\n1 garlic clove, minced
	\n4 carrots
	\n4 potatoes
	\n4 stalks celery
	\ncornstarch, to thicken</string>
    <string name="direction_five">
	\nHeat oil in dutch oven over medium high heat.
	\nBraise meat for about 5 minutes, turning often until browned on all sides.
	\nRemove, set aside and keep warm.
	\nSaute onions in dutch oven until limp.
	\nAdd broth, apple juice, wine, onion soup mix&amp; spices and stir well.
	\nReturn beef to dutch oven.
	\nRoast at 325°F for 2 1/2 hours, turning beef about every 30 minutes.
	\nCut vegetables into chunks, add to pot and cook for about another hour or until cooked to desired doneness.
	\nRemove veggies and beef and keep warm until ready to serve; for a thicker gravy, use corn starch.</string>
    <string name="recipe_name_six">Rheinisches Muschelessen</string>
    <string name="ingredient_six">
	\n6 -7 lbs mussels
	\n1 carrot, sliced
	\n1 leek, sliced
	\n1 onion, diced
	\n1⁄2 cup white wine
	\n1⁄4 cup water
	\n11 black peppercorns
	\n1⁄2 teaspoon salt
	\n1 bay leaf (optional)
	\n1 pinch nutmeg (optional)</string>
    <string name="direction_six">
	\nWash every mussel thouroughly. Scrub the shells (with a stiff brush, if necessary) and rinse under cold running water. Pull the stringy "beards" out of the mussels, but you can also leave them.
	\nDiscard any mussel, that is open. Keep them in cold water until use.
	\nBring all other ingredients in a large pot to a hard boil.
	\nAdd mussels and cook them for about 5 - 10 minutes or until all shells are opened. Do not overcook, as mussels will become tough and rubbery. Shake the pot during cooking, so that mussels are mixed.
	\nTake mussels out of the pot with a slotted spoon.
	\nServe them hot with some cooking fluid and veggies.
	\nNOTE: To eat mussels use an empty shell as a gripper.
	\nNOTE: For guests you can prepare the mussels in portions. So they are hot and can be served immediately from the cooking fluid.
	\nNOTE: Typically served with a coarse rye bread, butter, salt and a glas of beer.</string>
    <string name="recipe_name_seven">One-Pot Veggie Pasta</string>
    <string name="ingredient_seven">
	\n12 ounces linguine
	\n2 cups fresh broccoli florets
	\n1 cup fresh asparagus, cut into 1-inch pieces
	\n2 cups sliced zucchini
	\n1⁄2 cup fresh snow pea
	\n1⁄2 cup frozen green pea, thawed
	\n1⁄2 cup half-and-half cream
	\n1⁄2 cup parmesan cheese
	\n2 tablespoons butter, softened
	\n1⁄4 teaspoon salt
	\n1⁄4 teaspoon pepper</string>
    <string name="direction_seven">
	\nBring a large pot of water to a boil. Add linguine and boil 7 minutes, stirring occasionally.
	\nGradually, so that the water doesn\'t stop boiling, add broccoli and asparagus. Cook 2 minutes more.
	\nGradually add the zucchini, snow peas, and green peas. Cook 3 minutes longer.
	\nDuring this final cooking time, put the half &amp; half, parmesan, butter, salt, and pepper in a large serving bowl.
	\nDrain pasta and veggies well and immediately pour into the serving bowl. Toss to coat all with cream mixture. Serve at once.</string>
    <string name="recipe_name_eight">Pork Chops With Potatoes and Onions</string>
    <string name="ingredient_eight">
	\n2 tablespoons vegetable oil
	\n4 pork chops, trimmed (1/2 inch thick)
	\n2 tablespoons all-purpose flour
	\n1⁄3 cup parmesan cheese, grated
	\n1⁄2 teaspoon salt
	\n1⁄4 teaspoon pepper
	\n4 yukon gold potatoes, thinly sliced
	\n2 medium onions, sliced
	\n2 beef bouillon cubes
	\n3⁄4 cup hot water
	\n1 tablespoon lemon juice</string>
    <string name="direction_eight">
	\nHeat oil in a large skillet over medium heat.
	\nCoat the pork chops with flour, and place in the skillet.
	\nBrown about 4 minutes on each side.
	\nIn a small bowl, mix the Parmesan cheese, salt, and pepper.
	\nSprinkle 1/2 the Parmesan cheese mixture over the pork chops.
	\nLayer chops with the potatoes.
	\nSprinkle with remaining Parmesan cheese mixture.
	\nTop with onion slices.
	\nIn a small bowl, dissolve the beef bouillon cubes in hot water.
	\nStir in the lemon juice.
	\nPour over the layered pork chops.
	\nCover skillet, and reduce heat.
	\nSimmer 40 minutes, until vegetables are tender and pork chops have reached an internal temperature of 160°F (70°C).</string>
    <string name="recipe_name_nine">To Die for Crock Pot Roast</string>
    <string name="ingredient_nine">
	\n1 (4 -5 lb) beef roast, any kind
	\n1 (1 1/4 ounce) package brown gravy mix, dry
	\n1 (1 1/4 ounce) package dried Italian salad dressing mix
	\n1 (1 1/4 ounce) package ranch dressing mix, dry
	\n1⁄2 cup water</string>
    \n
    <string name="direction_nine">
	\nPlace beef roast in crock pot.
	\nMix the dried mixes together in a bowl and sprinkle over the roast.
	\nPour the water around the roast.
	\nCook on low for 7-9 hours.
	\nUse onion soup mix instead of ranch.
	\nAdd one cup,of red wine.
	\nAdd potatoes,carrots,mushrooms,celery and onion 2-3 hours before end.</string>
    <string name="recipe_name_ten">Potato Soup</string>
    <string name="ingredient_ten">
	\n4 cups cubed peeled potatoes
	\n1 1⁄4 cups water
	\n2 teaspoons chicken bouillon
	\n1 cup sliced celery
	\n1⁄2 cup chopped carrot
	\n1⁄2 cup chopped onion
	\n2 tablespoons snipped parsley
	\n1 1⁄2 teaspoons salt
	\n1⁄8 teaspoon pepper
	\n1 teaspoon dill weed
	\n4 cups milk
	\n3 tablespoons flour
	\n2 tablespoons butter
	\nbacon bits (to garnish)</string>
    <string name="direction_ten">
	\nIn saucepan combine potatoes, water, chicken bouillon, celery, carrot, onion, parsley, salt, pepper, dill weed and butter.
	\nCover and simmer until veggies are tender (about 15-20 minutes).
	\nAdd 3 1/2 cups of milk heat until hot.
	\nBlend flour with 1/2 cup milk stirring till smooth, then stir in soup.
	\nCook, stirring constantly until smooth and bubbly.
	\nSprinkle bacon bits over the top and serve</string>
    <string name="recipe_name_eleven">Spanish Chicken &amp; Rice Bake</string>
    <string name="ingredient_eleven">
	\n1 (10 3/4 ounce) can cream of chicken soup
	\n1 cup salsa
	\n1⁄2 cup water
	\n1 cup whole kernel corn
	\n3⁄4 cup uncooked long-grain white rice
	\n4 boneless chicken breast halves
	\n1⁄2 teaspoon chili powder
	\n1⁄2 cup shredded cheddar cheese
	\n1 cup canned black beans, washed (optional)</string>
    <string name="direction_eleven">
	\nMix soup, salsa, water, corn, and beans (optional) and rice in 2-quart shallow baking dish.
	\nTop with chicken (seasoned with salt and pepper) and sprinkle with chili powder.
	\nCover tightly with casserole lid or foil.
	\nBake at 375°F for 45 minutes or so.
	\nSprinkle with cheese.</string>
    <string name="recipe_name_twelve">Baja Black Beans, Corn and Rice</string>
    <string name="ingredient_twelve">
	\ncups cooked brown rice
	\n1 (15 ounce) can black beans, rinsed and drained
	\n1 (15 ounce) can corn, drained
	\n4 fresh tomatoes, diced
	\n1⁄2 cup red onion, chopped
	\n1⁄2 cup cilantro, chopped
	\n1 jalapeno pepper, seeded and diced
	\n2 tablespoons fresh lime juice
	\n1 tablespoon olive oil
	\n1⁄2 teaspoon salt
	\n1⁄4 teaspoon fresh ground pepper
	\n2 dashes hot sauce</string>
    <string name="direction_twelve">
	\nCook brown rice.
	\nIn a medium bowl, combine black beans, corn, tomatoes, onion, cilantro, jalapeno, lime juice, oil, salt, pepper and hot sauce.
	\nTo serve, Place a scoop of hot rice in a bowl or on a plate, top with a generous scoop of the black bean mixture.
	\nStir together before eating.</string>
    <string name="recipe_name_thirdteen">Chicken, Shrimp and Andouille Jambalaya</string>
    <string name="ingredient_thirdteen">
	\n2 tablespoons extra virgin olive oil
	\n1 1⁄2 lbs boneless skinless chicken thighs
	\n1 lb andouille sausage, cut into 1/4 inch slices
	\n1 large onion, chopped
	\n2 celery ribs, diced
	\n1⁄2green bell pepper, diced
	\n1⁄2red bell pepper, diced
	\n1⁄2 teaspoon dried thyme
	\n1⁄4 teaspoon dried oregano
	\n1⁄4 teaspoon sweet paprika
	\n1⁄2 teaspoon salt
	\n1⁄4-1⁄2 teaspoon cayenne pepper (optional)
	\n1 1⁄2 cups long grain rice
	\n1 (14 ounce) can tomatoes, chopped,with juice
	\n2 cups chicken broth or 2 cups stock
	\n8 ounces medium shrimp, peeled and deveined
	\n2 tablespoons chopped fresh parsley
	\n3 green onions, finely chopped</string>
    <string name="direction_thirdteen">
	\nPreheat oven to 350 degrees F.
	\nIn a large pan or Dutch oven, brown chicken in hot oil on both sides; remove and drain.
	\nAdd andouille, onion, celery, bell pepper, thyme, oregano, paprika, salt, and cayenne pepper to the pan, cooking and stirring for about 5 minutes until onions are tender.
	\nAdd rice, tomatoes with juice, and broth; bring to a boil.
	\nPlace rice mixture in a baking dish or oven-proof casserole; top with chicken; cover (can use foil) and bake at 350 degrees F for 40-45 minutes or until rice and chicken are done and tender.
	\nStir in shrimp, parsley, and green onions; cover and cook 5-8 minutes longer or until shrimp curl and turn bright pink and serve.</string>
    <string name="recipe_name_fourteen">Jambalaya for the Crock Pot</string>
    <string name="ingredient_fourteen">
	\n12 ounces boneless skinless chicken breasts
	\n1 1⁄2 cups green peppers, chopped
	\n1 medium onion, chopped
	\n2 celery ribs, sliced
	\n4 garlic cloves, minced
	\n1 (14 ounce) can whole tomatoes
	\n1⁄3 cup tomato paste
	\n1 (10 1/2 ounce) can beef broth
	\n1 tablespoon parsley
	\n1 1⁄2 teaspoons basil
	\n1⁄2 teaspoon oregano
	\n1 teaspoon Tabasco sauce
	\n1⁄2 teaspoon cayenne pepper
	\n1⁄2 teaspoon salt
	\n1 lb shrimp, shelled
	\n3 cups cooked rice</string>
    <string name="direction_fourteen">
	\nCut chicken into 1 inch pieces.
	\nPut all ingredients (EXCEPT shrimp and rice) in crock pot.
	\nCover; cook on low for 8 hours.
	\nAdd shrimp the last 20 minutes of cooking.
	\nStir in rice before serving.</string>
    <string name="recipe_name_fifthteen">Real English Fish and Chips With Yorkshire Beer Batter</string>
    <string name="ingredient_fifthteen">
	\n4 cod fish fillets or 4 haddock fillets
	\n6 ounces plain flour
	\n1 teaspoon bicarbonate of soda
	\n1 (8 fluid ounce) bottlebritish beer, Small
	\n1/2 lemon, juice of
	\nsalt &amp; pepper
	\nextra flour
	\n3 lbs potatoes, peeled &amp; chipped
	\ngood quality cooking fat or oil</string>
    <string name="direction_fifthteen">
	Heat fat up in a chip pan or automatic deep fat fryer - mine has a chip setting which is 190°C.
	\nPeel the potatoes and cut into chunky sized chips. Rinse and dry thoroughly.
	\nFry chips for about 3 minutes until soft but NOT coloured. Drain and shake well and set to one side.
	\nPut some flour onto a plate. Dredge the fish fillets in the flour thoroughly - this is VERY important, it stops the batter sliding off when fried! Leave the fish fillets in the flour whilst you make the batter.
	\nSome people say you should make the batter at least one hour before - I have found little difference - so make it before if it is convenient or now!
	\nPut flour, bicarbonate of soda, salt and pepper into a large roomy bowl. Add the beer gradually, stop when you have a thick coating type of batter. Drink any beer that is left! Whisk thoroughly until it is smooth and there are no lumps.Add the lemon juice OR a splash of malt vinegar if desired. Mix thoroughly again.
	\nHave your plates, newspaper or whatever ready for eating!
	\nAdjust deep fat fryer to fish frying temperature of 160°C.
	\nTake one fillet of fish at a time and holding it by the tail or thin end (!) swirl it around the batter until well coated - plunge into hot fat immediately. As soon as it has crisped up and set, add your other fillets one at a time, taking out the first ones as they cook - about 6 to 10 minutes depending on the thickness. Place onto a tray and keep warm in the oven.
	\nTurn up the heat setting to 190°C again and cook your chips until golden and crisp.
	\nServe on plates or newspaper with salt &amp; vinegar!
	\nAll you need now is a pint of warm beer and Coronation Street on the TV to set the scene!
	\nThis batter is great for small fish goujons, chicken goujons and also tempura vegetables too.</string>
    <string-array name="urls">
        <item>http://img.sndimg.com/food/image/upload/h_420,w_560,c_fit/v1/img/recipes/45/80/9/ggIfR8tpTUOkImhj16cV_DSC_1678-2.jpg</item>
        <item>http://img.sndimg.com/food/image/upload/h_420,w_560,c_fit/v1/img/recipes/27/49/20/picpJc2dP.jpg</item>
        <item>http://img.sndimg.com/food/image/upload/h_463,w_618,c_fit/v1/img/recipes/28/35/22/pic7yO7kQ.jpg</item>
        <item>http://img.sndimg.com/food/image/upload/h_420,w_560,c_fit/v1/img/recipes/44/94/52/picbE3WCb.jpg</item>
        <item>http://img.sndimg.com/food/image/upload/h_420,w_560,c_fit/v1/img/recipes/56/90/2/picAI1gR5.jpg</item>
        <item>http://img.sndimg.com/food/image/upload/h_420,w_560,c_fit/v1/img/recipes/14/08/92/picxzZRSL.jpg</item>
        <item>http://img.sndimg.com/food/image/upload/h_420,w_560,c_fit/v1/img/recipes/37/99/37/JpLgaeVbSY6VirN6kmhT_untitled-2653.jpg</item>
        <item>http://img.sndimg.com/food/image/upload/h_420,w_560,c_fit/v1/img/recipes/26/57/14/pic24EzkM.jpg</item>

        <item>http://img.sndimg.com/food/image/upload/h_420,w_560,c_fit/v1/img/recipes/27/20/8/picVfzLZo.jpg</item>

        <item>http://img.sndimg.com/food/image/upload/h_420,w_560,c_fit/v1/img/recipes/45/99/0/picVTYnJW.jpg</item>
        <item>http://img.sndimg.com/food/image/upload/h_463,w_618,c_fit/v1/img/recipes/31/51/6/picNdi7oF.jpg</item>
        <item>http://img.sndimg.com/food/image/upload/h_420,w_560,c_fit/v1/img/recipes/55/76/8/kASmFgkHRf6yPLmv9pLE_black-beans-and-corn-3.jpg</item>
        <item>http://img.sndimg.com/food/image/upload/h_420,w_560,c_fit/v1/img/recipes/28/16/5/picDUphVw.jpg</item>
        <item>http://img.sndimg.com/food/image/upload/h_420,w_560,c_fit/v1/img/recipes/41/70/5/6bZc8kzDR2WRvAaaoBf6_IMG_6171%20jambalaya.jpg</item>
        <item>http://img.sndimg.com/food/image/upload/h_420,w_560,c_fit/v1/img/recipes/18/33/99/picKiRxTG.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_change_back_ground">ChangeBackGroundActivity</string>


</resources>
